export default data = [
  {
      question: "Tom is really a naughty boy. He likes to _____ and play jokes on his younger sister when their parents are not around.",
      options: ["alert","spare","tease","oppose"],
      correct_option: "tease"
  },
  {
      question: "Elderly shoppers in this store are advised to take the elevator rather than the _____, which may move too fast for them to keep their balance.",
      options: ["airway","operator","escalator","instrument"],
      correct_option: "escalator"
  },
  {
      question: "Upon hearing its master’s call, the dog wagged its tail, and followed her out of the room _____.",
      options: ["obediently","apparently","logically","thoroughly"],
      correct_option: "obediently"
  },
  {
      question: "Since many of our house plants are from humid jungle environments, they need _____ air to keep them green and healthy.",
      options: ["moist","stale","crisp","fertile"],
      correct_option: "moist"
  },
  {
      question: "The skydiver managed to land safely after jumping out of the aircraft, even though her _____ failed to open in midair.",
      options: ["glimpse","latitude","segment","parachute"],
      correct_option: "parachute"
  },
  {
      question: "The invention of the steam engine, which was used to power heavy machines, brought about a _____ change in society.",
      options: ["persuasive","harmonious","conventional","revolutionary"],
      correct_option: "revolutionary"
  },
  {
      question: "To encourage classroom _____, the teacher divided the class into groups and asked them to solve a problem together with their partners.",
      options: ["operation","interaction","adjustment","explanation"],
      correct_option: "interaction"
  },
  {
      question: "Lisa _____ onto the ground and injured her ankle while she was playing basketball yesterday.",
      options: ["buried","punched","scattered","tumbled"],
      correct_option: "tumbled"
  },
  {
      question: "Hundreds of residents received free testing _____ from the city government to find out if their water contained any harmful chemicals.",
      options: ["kits","trials","zones","proofs"],
      correct_option: "kits"
  },
  {
      question: "The 2011 Nobel Peace Prize was awarded _____ to three women for the efforts they made in fighting for women’s rights.",
      options: ["actively","earnestly","jointly","naturally"],
      correct_option: "jointly"
  },
  {
      question: "The company is _____ and making great profits under the wise leadership of the chief executive officer.",
      options: ["applauding","flourishing","circulating","exceeding"],
      correct_option: "flourishing"
  },
  {
      question: "It is absolutely _____ to waste your money on an expensive car when you cannot even get a driver’s license.",
      options: ["absurd","cautious","vigorous","obstinate"],
      correct_option: "absurd"
  },
  {
      question: "The problem of illegal drug use is very complex and cannot be traced to merely one _____ reason.",
      options: ["singular","countable","favorable","defensive"],
      correct_option: "singular"
  },
  {
      question: "The non-profit organization has _____ $1 million over five years to finance the construction of the medical center.",
      options: ["equipped","resolved","committed","associated"],
      correct_option: "committed"
  },
  {
      question: "One week after the typhoon, some bridges were finally opened and bus service _____ in the country’s most severely damaged areas.",
      options: ["departed","resumed","transported","corresponded"],
      correct_option: "resumed"
  },
]